<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">网络流量防火</string>
    <string name="title_enabled">网络流量防火墙</string>
    <string name="title_disabled">网络流量防火墙 (Firewall disabled)</string>
    <string name="showrules">显示规则</string>
    <string name="applyrules">应用规则</string>
    <string name="saverules">保存规则</string>
    <string name="purgerules">清除规则</string>
    <string name="setpwd">设定密码</string>
    <string name="help">帮助</string>
    <string name="close">关闭</string>
    <string name="fw_enabled">防火墙打开</string>
    <string name="fw_disabled">防火墙关闭</string>
    <string name="log_enabled">日志打开</string>
    <string name="log_disabled">日志关闭</string>
    <string name="show_log">显示日志</string>
    <string name="clear_log">清除日志</string>
    <string name="pass_titleset">设置密码锁</string>
    <string name="pass_titleget">密码需求</string>
    <string name="enterpass">Enter the password:</string>
    <string name="enternewpass">Enter the new password (leave blank to remove):</string>
    <string name="toast_bin_installed">流量防火墙: 二进制文件已安装!</string>
    <string name="toast_error_enabling">&quot;防火墙l: 错误打开!&quot;</string>
	<string name="help_dialog_text"><i>Author: Rodrigo Zechin Rosauro</i>
		\n<i><a href="http://droidwall.googlecode.com">http://droidwall.googlecode.com</a></i>
		\n
		\n<i>DroidWall - Android Firewall</i> is a front-end application for the powerful <b>iptables</b> Linux firewall.
		It allows you to restrict which applications are permitted to access your data networks.
		\nThis is the perfect solution if you don\'t have an unlimited data plan, or just wants to see your battery lasting longer.
		\n
		\n<b>Using DroidWall:</b>
		\n<b>1.</b> Click on <b>Mode</b> to switch between <i>White List</i> and <i>Black List</i> modes.
		\n<b>2.</b> Mark the applications that you want to block or allow (depending on the selected mode), for each interface.
		\n<b>3.</b> Open the menu and enable the firewall. If the firewall is already enabled, just select <b>Apply rules</b>.
		\nThe rules will be saved and automatically restored when you restart your phone.
		\nIf want to check all current iptables rules, select <b>Show rules</b> in the menu.
		\n
		\n<b>Widget:</b>
		\nTo quickly enable or disable the firewall, add the DroidWall widget to your home screen.
		\n
		\n<b>Firewall logs:</b>
		\nIf you want to see which applications have been blocked by DroidWall, open the menu and enable the Log.
		\nDroidWall will then log each application blocked. You can check the log by opening the menu and selecting <b>More -> Show log</b>.
		\n
		\n<b>Password lock:</b>
		\nYou can set a password lock for DroidWall by using the <b>Set password</b> menu option.
		\nTo remove the password protection, just reset it to blank.
	</string>
</resources>
